泰安市二零二四年初中学业水平考试英语试题：听力。测试正式开始。一，听句子，选择适当的应答语。每个句子读两遍。
1. Would you like some noodles with chicken?
2. What does your mother do?
3. I think it's important to get enough sleep.
4. Your brother looks unhappy, what's wrong with him?
5. Tommy, remember to close the door when you leave the classroom.
二，听五段对话，选择正确答案。每段对话读两遍，你将有二十秒钟。时间阅读下面五个小题。
6. Lucy, what were you doing at 8 o last night?
7. Dave, when do you have P.E.
8. Where are you going on summer vacation?
9. I'm Kunming 9.
I help you sir?
10. I am interested in English.
11. What about you Peter?
12. Me too.
I try my best to learn English well, but I still have difficulty memorizing the
words. 14. sunny and warm.
三、听两段长对话，选择正确答案。每段对话读两遍。听每段对话前，你将有十秒钟的时间阅读对应的三个小题。听第一段对话，回答第十一至十三小题。
I also like the people here because they're friendly.
But the food is too expensive.
I see. Have you visited the Eiffel Tower?
16. I took the underground train there and saw many fantastic sights.
But I didn't take any photos.
Why? I left my camera in the hotel.
And even worse, my phone didn't work.
What a pity.
Now, listen again.
Hello Paul. Are you still in Paris now?
Yes, I arrived here the day before yesterday.
What's the weather like there?
Great. It's sunny and warm.
I also like the people here because they're friendly.
But the food is too expensive.
I see. Have you visited the Eiffel Tower?
Yes. I took the underground train there and saw many fantastic sights.
But I didn't take any photos.
Why? I left my camera in the hotel.
And even worse, my phone didn't work.
What a pity.
听第二段对话，回答第十四至十六小题。
Mike, do you know there is a new shopping mall on Center Street?
Oh, really? Yes.
It will open on Sunday, the day after tomorrow.
And there will be a big sale.
What do you want to buy?
I want to buy a skirt for Alice, and a t -shirt for Bob.
Would you like to go there with us?
I'm afraid not.
I have to visit my friend Jack.
He hurt his leg by accident yesterday, and he's at home now.
Oh, I'm sorry to hear that.
Now, listen again.
Mike, do you know there is a new shopping mall on Center Street?
Oh, really? Yes.
It will open on Sunday, the day after tomorrow.
And there will be a big sale.
What do you want to buy?
I want to buy a skirt for Alice, and a t -shirt for Bob.
Would you like to go there with us?
I'm afraid not.
I have to visit my friend Jack.
He hurt his leg by accident yesterday, and he's at home now.
Oh, I'm sorry to hear that.
四，听短文回答下面四个问题，选择正确答案。短文读两遍，你将有二十秒钟的时间。阅读下面四个小题。
Good morning, and girls.
Our company is now planning a short training program.
I want to take a little of your time to talk about it.
It's called Learning from Practice.
And the purpose is to develop your ability to be independent.
There will be classes on communication and management.
We also have colorful outdoor activities such as trees, growing vegetables and
camping. You don't need any experience.
Our company will receive a full report on your performance.
You'll be sure to improve your life skills and develop good habits.
The 10 -day program will be in August.
If you are interested, please write your name and telephone number on this
information card after the meeting.
Thank you. Now.
Listen again. Good morning, boys and girls.
Our company is now planning a short training program.
I want to take a little of your time to talk about it.
It's called Learning from Practice.
And the purpose is to develop your ability to be independent.
There will be classes on communication and management.
We also have colorful outdoor activities such as planting trees, growing vegetables
and camping. You don't need any experience.
Our company will receive a full report on your performance.
You'll be sure to improve your life skills and develop good habits.
The 10 -day program will be in August.
If you are interested, please write your name and telephone number on this
information card after the meeting.
Thank you. of Ladies and gentlemen,
五听短文填表格。根据短文内容。写出下面表格中所缺信息，每空一词。短文读三遍。你将有二十秒钟的时间阅读表格内容。答题完毕后，请将答案填写在答题卡的相应位置。
running is still the simplest way to exercise in our daily life.
The following suggestions may help you make your running pleasant and safe.
Firstly, it is important to buy a pair of comfortable running shoes.
They can protect your back, your feet and your legs from getting hurt.
Secondly, walk before you run.
For the first four weeks, you should have a 10 -minute warm -up walk before running.
Make sure you run and walk at least three times a week.
Please don't run if you're not feeling well.
Thirdly, run for time.
You should plan to slowly increase the running time rather than the kilometers.
Finally, be patient.
Don't be in hurry to take part in road races, no matter how much your friends expect
you. Wait until you can run 30 minutes without resting.
Are you ready to run now?
Now. Listen again.
Ladies and gentlemen, running is still the simplest way to exercise in our daily
life. The following suggestions may help you make your running pleasant and safe.
Firstly, it is important to buy a pair of comfortable running shoes.
They can protect your back, your feet and your legs from getting hurt.
Secondly, walk before you run.
For the first four weeks, you should have a 10 -minute warm -up walk before running.
Make sure you run and walk at least three times a
Please don't run if you're not feeling well.
Thirdly, run for time.
You should plan to slowly increase the running time rather than the kilometers.
Finally, be patient.
Don't be in hurry to take part in road races, no matter how much your friends expect
you. Wait until you can run 30 minutes without resting.
Are you ready to run now?
Now. Listen again.
Ladies and gentlemen,
running is still the simplest way to exercise in our daily life.
following suggestions may help you make your running pleasant and safe.
Firstly, it is important to buy a pair of comfortable running shoes.
They can protect your back, your feet and your legs from getting hurt.
Secondly, walk before you run.
For the first four weeks, you should have a 10 -minute warm -up walk before running.
Make sure you run and walk at least three times a week.
Please don't run if you're not feeling well.
Thirdly, run for time.
You should plan to slowly increase the running time rather than the kilometers.
Finally, be patient.
Don't be in hurry to take part in road races, no matter how much your friends expect
you. Wait until you can run 30 minutes without resting.
Are you ready to run now?
听力测试到此结束，请同学们继续做其他题目。